Narrator: 1
A: Did you manage to agree anything with your ex-wife?
B: No, we went back and forth for hours, but we just couldn’t agree.
Narrator: 2
A: Did you think you’d finish the marathon?
B: I wasn’t sure, but once I got to the park, I knew I was home and dry.
Narrator: 3
A: Did you ever get back that money from your brother?
B: No, I didn’t. Oh, well, you live and learn.
Narrator: 4
A: But, Mum, I don’t want to work in a café this summer.
B: You can’t pick and choose – just take any job you can get.
Narrator: 5
A: Your job sounds quite complicated. Is it?
B: Well, it takes a while to learn all the ins and outs.
Narrator: 6
A: Did you sleep OK last night?
B: Not really, it was too hot. I tossed and turned for hours.